Political Research Associates Records MS014
Tufts Archival Research Center
Political Research Associates Records
1908 -- 2019
Tufts Archival Research Center
Political Research Associates
MS014
226.2 Linear Feet
3 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
This collection contains materials created and collected by Political Research Associates including publications; research files that contain direct mail, promotional materials, news clippings, and speeches; subject files; videos; and an archived website. Materials relate to right-wing organizations, persons, and activities.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Biographical / Historical
In 1981, Political Research Associates began exposing the broad spectrum of right-wing violence through in-depth analysis of founding directors Jean Hardisty and Chip Berlet. Originally known as Midwest Research and based in Chicago, it quickly became known for its work in support of racial justice. In 1987, Citizens Alert recognized the think tank with its Rev. Willie Baker Award for "outstanding efforts" working for racial justice in Chicago by helping anti-racism activists understand how white supremacist and antisemitic groups mobilized support in neighborhoods.
By 1987, the organization had moved to Boston, changed its name to Political Research Associates, and expanded the range of the political Right that it analyzed. In 1991, PRA launched a collaboration with South End Press with the publication of two books by Russ Bellant: The Coors Connection: How Coors Family Philanthropy Undermines Democratic Pluralism, and Old Nazis, the New Right, and the Republican Party. The next year, it began publication of its magazine The Public Eye to present the latest research on the US Right for use by advocates and journalists, while continuing to issue special reports.
During its history, PRA has provided research on Posse Comitatus, the militia movement, neo-Nazis, the Christian Right, conservative think tanks, anti-immigrant movements, and government repression.
Custodial History
The first accession of materials from the PRA was transferred directly to Personal Movers Storage. The 2017 accession was packed at PRA by DCA staff and transferred directly to Iron Mountain.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of materials created and collected by Political Research Associates. It includes publications, research and subject files, videos, and historical web archives of Political Research Associates' website. Publications were created by political, social, and religious organizations as well as hate groups and watchdog organizations, mostly in the United States, and were collected by PRA. The materials are largely professional publications and span from 1908 to 2011. Research files date from 1923 to 2010 and were compiled by former PRA senior analyst Chip Berlet. They include publications, clippings, notes, correspondence, articles by Berlet, PRA organizational records, PRA publications, promotional materials and direct mail from right-wing organizations, and materials from speeches and conferences at which Berlet spoke. Subject files were compiled by PRA staff on various right-wing political, social, and religious organizations, as well as related subjects and events. Subject files include newspaper clippings, fliers, pamphlets, newsletters, academic reports, white papers, correspondence, direct mail, handbooks, reference copies, ephemera and artifacts on topics pertaining to right-wing political groups and movements, dating from approximately 1949 to 2010. A small number of videos document events related to conservative Christian groups, dated 2005-2006. Web archives of PRA's website date back to 2013 and are updated yearly. Throughout the collection, major themes include right-wing extremism, antisemitism, anti-abortion violence, nativism, racism, traditional family values, anti-LGBT issues, social justice, and human rights monitoring.
Content Warning
This collection contains materials created by conservative groups across the United States, and research materials about these groups. These materials deal with topics including right-wing extremism, anti-Semitism, anti-abortion violence, nativism, racism, traditional family values, sexual assault, child abuse, anti-LGBT issues, the Klu Klux Klan, the Nazi Party, white supremacy, women's rights, social justice, and human rights monitoring. Materials in this collection contain images and rhetoric that is antisemitic, racist, homophobic, and misogynist, as well as images depicting graphic violence and graphic sexual content.
This finding aid contains language that may be offensive or outdated. Because such language is in direct transcription of existing older titles or of published materials, it has not been changed. Keeping this language intact provides the most accurate depiction of the creators' intent, and can potentially tell us important things about bigotry and bias on the part of the creators, or in a particular historical context. It can also preserve terms formerly applied by a group to self-identify that have since fallen out of common usage.
For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
Related Materials
John Birch Society Records, 1928-1990. Brown University. Providence, Rhode Island.
Arrangement
The records are arranged into five series: 1. Publications, 2. Chip Berlet Research Files, 3. Subject Files, 4. Videos, and 5. Website.
Right-wing extremists; Human rights monitoring; Social justice
- Publications, 1908 -- 2011; MS014.001; 91.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series is comprised of publications collected by Political Research Associates for its reference library. In general, materials in this series are not published by PRA itself, but by political, social, and religious organizations as well as hate groups and watchdog organizations. For publications created by PRA, please see Series 002. Publications that are widely available in other libraries (such as Time magazine) and/or are available as electronic journals were weeded from this collection.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by title of publication, and then chronologically within each title range. Photocopies of single articles are generally arranged by title in "Individual articles" folders at the end of each letter range. For example, an article titled "Immigration Reform" might be included in the "Individual 'I' articles" folder at the end of the "I" range. Please note: there is no Box 21.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - A: The Abortion Magazine, 2006; MS014.001.001.00001; Ipas (Box 1)
  - AACC News, 1981; MS014.001.001.00002; Affirmative Action Coordinating Center (Box 1)
  - ABA Watch, 2001 -- 2008; MS014.001.001.00003; The Federalist Society for Law and Public Policy Studies (Box 1)
  - Abate of Wisconsin Newsletter, 1998; MS014.001.001.00004; A.B.A.T.E A Brotherhood Against Totalitarian Enactments (Box 1)
  - Abiding Truth, 1998; MS014.001.001.00005; Abiding Turth Ministries (Box 1)
  - Abortion and the Constitution: Reversing Roe vs. Wade Through the Courts, 1987; MS014.001.001.00006; Americans United for Life (Box 1)
  - Above the Law, 1991; MS014.001.001.00007; ACLU Arts Censorship Project (Box 1)
  - Access the key to pro-life victory, 1998; MS014.001.001.00008; Life Dynamics Incorporated (Box 1)
  - Access to Energy, 1990 -- 1998; MS014.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - The ACLU vs America, 2005; MS014.001.001.00010; Broadman & Holman Publishers (Box 1)
  - ACLU, 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.001.00011; American Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts (Box 1)
  - Action, 1994 -- 2004; MS014.001.001.00012; National Coalition of Education Activists (Box 1)
  - Action [1 of 2], 1998 -- 1999; MS014.001.001.00013; The Rutherford Institute (Box 1)
  - Action [2 of 2], 1996 -- 1999; MS014.001.001.00014; The Rutherford Institute (Box 1)
  - Action Alert, 1998 -- 1999; MS014.001.001.00015; International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission (Box 1)
  - Action News, 1982 -- 1998; MS014.001.001.00016; Pro-Life Action League (Box 1)
  - Actions Speak Louder, 1993; MS014.001.001.00017; Catholics for Free Choice (Box 1)
  - Acts and Facts [1 of 3], 1999 -- 2000; MS014.001.001.00018; Institute for Creation Research (Box 1)
  - Acts and Facts [2 of 3], 1994 -- 1999; MS014.001.001.00019; Institute for Creation Research (Box 1)
  - Acts and Facts [3 of 3], 1995 -- 1997; MS014.001.001.00020; Institute for Creation Research (Box 1)
  - ACU, 1976; MS014.001.001.00021; American Conservative Union (Box 1)
  - Acumen, 1984; MS014.001.001.00022; American Conservative Union (Box 1)
  - ADA, MS014.001.001.00023; Americans for Democratic Action (Box 1)
  - ADAMH News, MS014.001.001.00024; Alcohol, Drug Abuse, and Mental Health Administration (Box 1)
  - The Adoremus Bulletin, 1995 -- 2007; MS014.001.001.00025; Adoremus (Box 1)
  - Adverse Impact!, 1999; MS014.001.001.00026; Applied Research Center (Box 1)
  - Advisory, 2007; MS014.001.001.00027; Criminal Justice Legal Foundation (Box 1)
  - The Advocate, 1991; MS014.001.001.00028; Advocates for Life (Box 1)
  - Advocate for America's Children, 1986; MS014.001.001.00029; National PTA (Box 1)
  - Aerious: Journal of Metaphysics, 1996; MS014.001.001.00030; Aerious (Box 1)
  - AFF News, 1996 -- 1997; MS014.001.001.00031; AFF (Box 1)
  - African-Americana Rare and Interesting Items, MS014.001.001.00032; McBlain Books (Box 1)
  - Afterimage, 1995; MS014.001.001.00033; Visual Studies Workshop (Box 1)
  - Against the Current, 1986; MS014.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Agenda, 1992 -- 1994; MS014.001.001.00035; National Council of La Raza (Box 1)
  - Ahoranow, 2005; MS014.001.001.00036; Labor/Community Strategy Center (Box 1)
  - AIDS Prevention, 1987 -- 1988; MS014.001.001.00037; National AIDS Prevention Institute (Box 1)
  - AIDS Protection, 1987 -- 1988; MS014.001.001.00038; National AIDS Prevention Institute (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [1 of 13], 1990 -- 1991; MS014.001.001.00039; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [2 of 13], 1989 -- 1990; MS014.001.001.00040; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [3 of 13], 1987 -- 1989; MS014.001.001.00041; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [4 of 13], 1985 -- 1987; MS014.001.001.00042; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [5 of 13], 1983 -- 1985; MS014.001.001.00043; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [6 of 13], 1977 -- 1983; MS014.001.001.00044; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [7 of 13], 1993 -- 1996; MS014.001.001.00045; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [8 of 13], 1995 -- 1996; MS014.001.001.00046; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 1)
  - AIM Report [9 of 13], 1994 -- 1995; MS014.001.002.00001; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 2)
  - AIM Report [10 of 13], 1993 -- 2006; MS014.001.002.00002; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 2)
  - AIM Report [11 of 13], 2003 -- 2008; MS014.001.002.00003; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 2)
  - AIM Report [12 of 13], 2004 -- 2006; MS014.001.002.00004; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 2)
  - AIM Report [13 of 13], 2006 -- 2009; MS014.001.002.00005; Accuracy in Media, Inc. (Box 2)
  - AJR, 1994; MS014.001.002.00006; Business Publications Audit of Circulation, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Akwesasne Notes, 1992; MS014.001.002.00007; Mohawk Nation (Box 2)
  - Alamo Christian Ministries World Newsletter, 2003; MS014.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - The Alan Stang Report, 1976 -- 1979; MS014.001.002.00009; The John Birch Society Features (Box 2)
  - The Alarming Cry, 1989 -- 1992; MS014.001.002.00010; Biblical Enterprises (Box 2)
  - Alexander Hamilton: How The Mighty Are Redeemed, 2000; MS014.001.002.00011; The Washington Fellowship of Family Research Council (Box 2)
  - Algebra Project News-letter, 2003; MS014.001.002.00012; Algebra Project, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Alkebulanian, 1990; MS014.001.002.00013; Alkebulans, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All About Issues [1 of 5], 1985 -- 1993; MS014.001.002.00014; American Life Lobby; American Life League, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All About Issues [2 of 5], 1985 -- 1987; MS014.001.002.00015; American Life Lobby; American Life League, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All About Issues [3 of 5], 1982 -- 1983; MS014.001.002.00016; American Life Lobby; American Life League, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All About Issues [4 of 5], 1984 -- 1985; MS014.001.002.00017; American Life Lobby; American Life League, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All About Issues [5 of 5], 1981 -- 1982; MS014.001.002.00018; American Life Lobby; American Life League, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All Citizens Equal|ACE Newsletter, 1992; MS014.001.002.00019; All Citizens Equal (Box 2)
  - A.L.L. Good News, 1995; MS014.001.002.00020; American Life League (Box 2)
  - ALL News, 1984 -- 1990; MS014.001.002.00021; American Life Lobby; American Life League, Inc. (Box 2)
  - All The Way, 1987 -- 1996; MS014.001.002.00022; The Nationalist Movement (Box 2)
  - All Things New, 2002; MS014.001.002.00023; Student Christian Movement of Canada (Box 2)
  - Alliance Alerts, 2000; MS014.001.002.00024; Alliance for Democracy (Box 2)
  - Alternative Press, 2005; MS014.001.002.00025; Alternatives for Community and Environment (ACE) (Box 2)
  - An Alternative U.S. Policy Toward Cuba, 1990; MS014.001.002.00026; Policy Alternatives for the Caribbean and Central America (Box 2)
  - AMAC Advantage, MS014.001.002.00027; Association of Mature American Citizens (Box 2)
  - The Ambassador, 2003 -- 2005; MS014.001.002.00028; American Indian Ambassadors Program (Box 2)
  - America @ Work, 1998 -- 1999; MS014.001.002.00029; AFL-CIO Public Affairs Department (Box 2)
  - America Needs Fatima, 1985 -- 1997; MS014.001.002.00030; The American Society for the Defense of Tradition, Family and Property (Box 2)
  - The American, 2004; MS014.001.002.00031; The American Cause (Box 2)
  - The American, 2001; MS014.001.002.00032; The American Party of the United States (Box 2)
  - American Atheist Newsletter, 1996; MS014.001.002.00033; American Aethists, Inc. (Box 2)
  - American Bible Society Record, 2000 -- 2001; MS014.001.002.00034; American Bible Society (Box 2)
  - The American Bulletin, 1990; MS014.001.002.00035; Czechoslovak National Council of America (Box 2)
  - American Capsule News, 1961 -- 1966; MS014.001.003.00001; Capsule News Company (Box 3)
  - American Christian Prompter, 1999; MS014.001.003.00002; The Foundation for the American Christian Education (Box 3)
  - The American Conservative [1 of 4], 1991 -- 1993; MS014.001.003.00003; The American Conservative (Box 3)
  - The American Conservative [2 of 4], 2002 -- 2004; MS014.001.003.00004; The American Conservative (Box 3)
  - The American Conservative [3 of 4], 2003; MS014.001.003.00005; The American Conservative (Box 3)
  - The American Conservative [4 of 4], 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.003.00006; The American Conservative (Box 3)
  - The American Conservative Union's Rating of Congress, 1976; MS014.001.003.00007; American Conservative Union (Box 3)
  - American Family Association Journal [1 of 4], 1990 -- 2000; MS014.001.003.00008; American Family Association (Box 3)
  - American Family Association Journal [2 of 4], 2000 -- 2006; MS014.001.003.00009; American Family Association (Box 3)
  - American Family Association Journal [3 of 4], 1992 -- 1999; MS014.001.003.00010; American Family Association (Box 3)
  - American Family Association Journal [4 of 4], 2002 -- 2009; MS014.001.003.00011; American Family Association (Box 3)
  - The American Feminist, 1995; MS014.001.003.00012; Feminists for Life of America (Box 3)
  - American Foreign Policy Interests, 1995 -- 2000; MS014.001.003.00013; National Committee on American Foreign Policy (Box 3)
  - American Foreign Policy Newsletter, 1989 -- 1991; MS014.001.003.00014; National Committee on American Foreign Policy (Box 3)
  - American Free Press [Folder 1 of 3], 2008; MS014.001.003.00015; American Free Press (Box 3)
  - American Free Press [Folder 2 of 3], 2008; MS014.001.003.00016; American Free Press (Box 3)
  - American Free Press [Folder 3 of 3], 2008; MS014.001.003.00017; American Free Press (Box 3)
  - American Freedom Journal [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1992; MS014.001.003.00018; American Freedom Coalition (Box 3)
  - American Freedom Journal [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1990; MS014.001.003.00019; American Freedom Coalition (Box 3)
  - American Freedom Magazine, 1996 -- 2002; MS014.001.003.00020; American Freedom Network (Box 3)
  - The American Hispanic, 1991; MS014.001.003.00021; Republican National Hispanic Assembly (Box 3)
  - The American Independent [1 of 3], 1990 -- 2006; MS014.001.004.00001; William K. Shearer (Box 4)
  - The American Independent [2 of 3], 1974 -- 2007; MS014.001.004.00002; William K. Shearer (Box 4)
  - The American Independent [3 of 3], 1991 -- 2004; MS014.001.004.00003; William K. Shearer (Box 4)
  - American Information Newsletter, 1992; MS014.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - American Juror, 2004 -- 2007; MS014.001.004.00005; Fully Informed Jury Association and the American Jury Institute (Box 4)
  - The American Lancer, 1981 -- 1986; MS014.001.004.00006; America First Committee, Inc. (Box 4)
  - American Legion Firing Line, 1991 -- 1992; MS014.001.004.00007; The American Legion (Box 4)
  - American Life League Publications, 2000 -- 2001; MS014.001.004.00008; American Life League (Box 4)
  - The American Mercury Religious Supplement, MS014.001.004.00009; American Mercury (Box 4)
  - American Nationalist, 1981; MS014.001.004.00010; Committee of Ten Million (Box 4)
  - American Opinion Preview Series|Seventeen Eighty Nine, 1999; MS014.001.004.00011; American Opinion (Box 4)
  - American Outlook, 1988; MS014.001.004.00012; The Hudson Institute (Box 4)
  - The American Patriot, 1981 -- 1982; MS014.001.004.00013; We, The People (Box 4)
  - American Postal Workers Union News Service, 2001; MS014.001.004.00014; American Postal Workers Union, AFL-CIO (Box 4)
  - American Relations, 1992; MS014.001.004.00015; The Institute of American Relations (Box 4)
  - American Quilt, 2000; MS014.001.004.00016; Scholastic (Box 4)
  - American Renaissance [1 of 2], 1992 -- 2003; MS014.001.004.00017; New Century Foundation (Box 4)
  - American Renaissance [2 of 2], 2003 -- 2004; MS014.001.004.00018; New Century Foundation (Box 4)
  - American Rights Guardian Update, 1979 -- 1983; MS014.001.004.00019; Protect Americans' Rights and Resources to Maintain an Informed Membership (Box 4)
  - American Sentinel [1 of 8], 1982 -- 1986; MS014.001.004.00020; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 4)
  - American Sentinel [2 of 8], 1988 -- 1997; MS014.001.004.00021; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 4)
  - American Sentinel [3 of 8], 1984 -- 1987; MS014.001.004.00022; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 4)
  - American Sentinel [4 of 8], 1993 -- 1994; MS014.001.005.00001; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 5)
  - American Sentinel [5 of 8], 1995 -- 1996; MS014.001.005.00002; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 5)
  - American Sentinel [6 of 8], 1997 -- 1998; MS014.001.005.00003; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 5)
  - American Sentinel [7 of 8], 1999 -- 2001; MS014.001.005.00004; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 5)
  - American Sentinel [8 of 8], 2002 -- 2009; MS014.001.005.00005; Phillips Publishing, Inc. (Box 5)
  - American Sroboran, 1996; MS014.001.005.00006; Sern National Federation (Box 5)
  - American Survival Guide, 1985 -- 1998; MS014.001.005.00007; McMullen Argus Publishing, Inc. (Box 5)
  - American Veterans Committee Bulletin, 1994 -- 2003; MS014.001.005.00008; American Veterans Committee (Box 5)
  - American Writer [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1998; MS014.001.005.00009; National Writers Union (Box 5)
  - American Writer [2 of 2], 1982 -- 1983; MS014.001.005.00010; National Writers Union (Box 5)
  - Americanist Issues, 2006; MS014.001.005.00011; American Opinion (Box 5)
  - Americans for Tax Reform Publications, 2009; MS014.001.005.00012; Americans for Tax Reform Foundation (Box 5)
  - The American's Bulletin [1 of 3], 1996 -- 2000; MS014.001.005.00013; A.B.S. Book Publishers (Box 5)
  - The American's Bulletin [2 of 3], 2001 -- 2003; MS014.001.005.00014; A.B.S. Book Publishers (Box 5)
  - The American's Bulletin [3 of 3], 1996 -- 2003; MS014.001.005.00015; A.B.S. Book Publishers (Box 5)
  - America's 1st Freedom, 2007 -- 2009; MS014.001.006.00001; National Rifle Association (Box 6)
  - America's Future [1 of 2], 1977 -- 1985; MS014.001.006.00002; America's Future, Inc. (Box 6)
  - America's Future [2 of 2], 1986 -- 1995; MS014.001.006.00003; America's Future, Inc. (Box 6)
  - America's God and Country Encyclopedia of Quotations, 2000; MS014.001.006.00004; Amerisearch, Inc. (Box 6)
  - America's Promise Newsletter, 1983 -- 1991; MS014.001.006.00005; Lord's Covenant Church Broadcast; America's Promise Broadcast (Box 6)
  - America's War on Poverty, 1985; MS014.001.006.00006; The Civil Rights Project, Inc. (Box 6)
  - Amnesty, 1974; MS014.001.006.00007; National Campus Alliance for Amnesty; United states National Student Association (Box 6)
  - Amnesty Action, 1990 -- 1993; MS014.001.006.00008; Amnesty International USA (Box 6)
  - Amnesty International, 2005 -- 2008; MS014.001.006.00009; Amnesty International USA (Box 6)
  - Amnesty Now, 2003; MS014.001.006.00010; Amnesty International USA (Box 6)
  - Anarchist Review, 1982; MS014.001.006.00011; Cienfuegos Press (Box 6)
  - Annales d'Histoire Revisionniste, 1987; MS014.001.006.00012; Nouvelles Messageries de la Presse Parisienne (Box 6)
  - Another idea for the Big Bang, MS014.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Anti-Abortion Violence Watch, 1997 -- 2000; MS014.001.006.00014; Feminist Majority Foundation; National Clinic Access Project (Box 6)
  - Antifa Forum, 1999; MS014.001.006.00015; Anti-Fascist Forum (Box 6)
  - Anti-Sexism Newsletter, 1990; MS014.001.006.00016; Lesbian & Gay Rights Subcomittee; National Committee to Combat Women's Oppression (Box 6)
  - AntiShyster, 1990 -- 1992; MS014.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Answer Magazine, 2000 -- 2002; MS014.001.006.00018; Gospel Publishing Association (Box 6)
  - APIRH (Asians & Pacific Islanders for Reproductive Health), 2000; MS014.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - APRA News, 1979 -- 1984; MS014.001.006.00020; American Pistol & Rifle Association (Box 6)
  - ARA News, 1994 -- 1998; MS014.001.006.00021; Anti-Racist Action; Columbus Institute for Contemporary Journalism (Box 6)
  - ARA Research Bulletin, 2001 -- 2002; MS014.001.006.00022; Anti-Racist Action Network (Box 6)
  - ARC News & Notes, 2005; MS014.001.006.00023; Applied Research Center (Box 6)
  - Are You Y2k-Proof?, 1999; MS014.001.006.00024; Year 2000 Alert (Box 6)
  - Around the Circle, 2004 -- 2009; MS014.001.006.00025; The Center for Information & Research on Civic Learning & Engagement (Box 6)
  - Arrows of Truth, MS014.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Arts Censorship Project Newsletter, 1991 -- 1995; MS014.001.006.00027; American Civil Liberties Union Arts Censorship Project (Box 6)
  - Aryan Action Line, 1992; MS014.001.006.00028; SS Action Group (Box 6)
  - Aryan Identity Fellowship, 1989; MS014.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Aryan Nations Newsletter, MS014.001.006.00030; Church of Jesus Christ Christian-Aryan Nations (Box 6)
  - Aryan Research Fellowship, 1990; MS014.001.006.00031; Stoddard Publishers (Box 6)
  - As the South Goes, 1996 -- 2003; MS014.001.006.00032; Project South: Institute for the Elimination of Poverty & Genocide (Box 6)
  - Asia, Inc., 1993; MS014.001.006.00033; Asia, Inc., Limited; Manager Publishing Group of Bangkok (Box 6)
  - Asia Insights, 1986; MS014.001.006.00034; Asia Resource Center (Box 6)
  - Associated Pregnancy Counseling Center, MS014.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Astraea: Lesbian Foundation for Justice, 2004 -- 2005; MS014.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - AUL Forum, 1998 -- 1999; MS014.001.006.00037; Americans United for Life (Box 6)